[
    {
        "front": "タバコ",
        "back": "Cigarette",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほしい",
        "back": "Need, Want  \n<adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようじ",
        "back": "Work, appointment",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいます",
        "back": "To smoke",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "そして",
        "back": "And (For sentences)",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "おみやげ",
        "back": "Souvenir, Gift",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねんかん",
        "back": "Period of years",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんしゅう",
        "back": "Last week",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんしゅう",
        "back": "This week",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいしゅう",
        "back": "Next week",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "また",
        "back": "Again",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざっねん",
        "back": "Unfortunate",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ときどき",
        "back": "Sometimes",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさ",
        "back": "Morning",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひる",
        "back": "Noon",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "よる",
        "back": "Night",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "たのしい",
        "back": "Enjoyable",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいきん",
        "back": "Now a days",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "たくさん",
        "back": "Too much\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうがた",
        "back": "Late evening",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "が / でも",
        "back": "But, However (polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "はなします",
        "back": "To speak",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かきます",
        "back": "To write",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "あるきます",
        "back": "To walk",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "います",
        "back": "To exist (Living things)",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "あります",
        "back": "To exist (Non-Living things)",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "おきます",
        "back": "To wake up",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねます",
        "back": "To sleep",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "はたらきます",
        "back": "To Work",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかね",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "~から / ~ので",
        "back": "‘therefore’",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんり",
        "back": "Convenient\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんせつ",
        "back": "Kind\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "しずか",
        "back": "Quiet\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうめい",
        "back": "Famous\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "きれい",
        "back": "Beautiful\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "やさい",
        "back": "Vegetable",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんき",
        "back": "Weather",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかてつ",
        "back": "Subway",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "もう",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう",
        "back": "Studies",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいます",
        "back": "To buy",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "メキシコ",
        "back": "Mexico",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "という",
        "back": "Called as",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさごはん",
        "back": "Breakfast",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "もっています",
        "back": "To have",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    },
    {
        "front": "おねがいします",
        "back": "to request, to wish, to ask, to beg",
        "chapter": "N5 C7"
    }
]